[Music]
Heat. Heat.
bridge is empty dancing a joke. Once
epic and some giant dope forward shot,
but we slept instead. Now we're
starving, full of thread.
Stomach's rumbling.
Now the clock strikes six.
We argue and we disagree. Pick and mix.
You want sushi? I want f and shakes.
Round and round. Another bite. You want
to take
oh
[Music]
meet us on my phone.
We scroll for an hour.
You say you're vegan now. You want to
call a flower. I just want burritos
or maybe some wings.
Why does dinner turn to a million
things?
We had breakfast cold
and lunch was late. They say food gra,
but this might break a
stomach from lane. Now the clock strike
sips.
We argue and we disagree. Pick and mix.
You want sushi? I want flies and shakes
round and round. Another bite. You want
to change?
[Music]